export const OrganismWorksheetsLink = {
  worksheet1: {
    title: "Organism Worksheets 1",
    link: "#",
  },
  worksheet2: {
    title: "Organism Worksheets 2",
    link: "#",
  },
  worksheet3: {
    title: "Organism Worksheets 3",
    link: "#",
  },

  worksheet4: {
    title: "Organism Worksheets 4",
    link: "#",
  },

  evaluation: {
    title: "Written Evaluation Form",
    link: "#",
  },
};

export const OrganismQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "The following practices should be observed in order to sustain feeding process in the ecosystem",
    choices: [
      "Raise animals and insects to fight other pests. ",
      "Dump organic wastes into rivers and streams. ",
      "Grow a variety of crops instead of only one crop. ",
      "Use organic fertilizers instead of chemical fertilizers. ",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "C" || "c",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "The food chain is characterized as a simple illustration of who eats and ",
    choices: ["One path", "Two paths", "Three paths", "Four path"],
    correctAnswer: "A" || "a",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which of the following organisms will a first-order consumer eat? ",
    choices: ["Giraffes", "Grasses", "Goats", "Grasshoppers"],
    correctAnswer: "C" || "c" || "D" || "d",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Which consumer in a trophic level can eat both plants and animals? ",
    choices: ["Carnivores", "Herbivores", "Decomposers", "Omnivores"],
    correctAnswer: "D" || "d",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Which of the following shows the correct sequence of feeding relationships in a food chain",
    choices: [
      "Grasses—Grasshoppers—Frogs—Snakes-- Eagle ",
      "Grasshoppers –Grasses—Frogs—Snakes-- Eagle ",
      "Frogs--- Snakes--- Eagle--- Grasses--- Grasshoppers ",
      "Snakes--- Eagle--- Frogs--- Grasses--- Grasshoppers  ",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A" || "a",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "If 600 kg of biomass is at the third trophic level, how much biomass was available at the first trophic level? ",
    choices: ["60 kg ", "600 kg", "6,000 kg", "60,000 kg "],
    correctAnswer: "D" || "d",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "If there are 100,000 kilocalories of energy in the first trophic level, how many kilocalories are available to organisms in the second trophic level? ",
    choices: [
      "100 kilocalories",
      "1000 kilocalories",
      "10,000 kilocalories",
      "100,000 kilocalories",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "C" || "c",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which of the following organisms are placed at the base of the energy pyramid?",
    choices: ["Carnivores", "Decomposers", "Omnivores", "Producers"],
    correctAnswer: "D" || "d",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which consumer helps with the recycling of nutrients? ",
    choices: ["Carnivore ", "Decomposer ", "Herbivore", "Omnivore"],
    correctAnswer: "B" || "b",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which of the following explains why fruit and vegetables eaters are energy efficient? ",
    choices: [
      "They do not use energy at all. ",
      "They burn much of their energy in a day.  ",
      "They directly derive energy from the producer level. ",
      "They get their energy from first-degree consumer level.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "C" || "c",
  },
];
